✿✿✿ Internet Download Manager ✿✿✿

Just install and browser integration will be done automatically. If it's not the case then...

For Chrome, Opera, Brave...
1. Open the browser and from menu click "More Tools" and then "Extensions".
2. Now drag and drop "IDM For Chrome" on the extensions space and press "Add".
3. If it fails, visit this link https://bit.ly/idm-chrome and add it to the browser.

For Edge...
1. Open the browser and from menu click "Extensions".
2. Now drag and drop "IDM For Edge" on the extensions space and press "Add".
3. If it fails, visit this link https://bit.ly/idm-edge and add it to the browser.

For Firefox...
1. Open the browser and from menu click "Add-ons" and then "Extensions".
2. Now drag and drop "IDM For Firefox" on the extensions space and press "Add".
3. If it fails, visit this link https://bit.ly/idm-firefox and add it to the browser.

And enjoy the Internet Download Manager latest version...


